http://www.natcofoods.com/en/privacy

Privacy Policy
Please read these terms of use carefully before using the site
NATCO FOODS maintains this Web Site and all the information, communications, software, scripting, photos, text, video, graphics, music, sounds, images and other materials and services found on the Site (collectively 'Content'), for the use of its customers, employees and members of the general public but only for the lawful purposes described below. Such content is provided by NATCO FOODS as a convenience to its customers and to the general public.
Please be aware that authorised Natco Foods Ltd recruitment personnel will never ask for money from prospective employees and anyone being asked to send money in this respect should not do so. If you are unsure about the authenticity of a job offer or are asked for money to progress a job application or otherwise feel uncomfortable about any aspect of the recruitment process, please do not send your personal details or any money. If you would like to check the authenticity of any Natco Foods Ltd job offer you have received, you should send an email to hr@natcofoods.com.
This privacy statement (also referred to as Natco’s Privacy Policy) explains our privacy practices for our customers and business contacts who interact with us in the course of our business activities.  It also covers those who shop online or in our Cash and Carry or use our websites - www.natcofoods.com. or www.natcocc.com.
Natco’s Commitment to Privacy
We respect your right to privacy. This privacy statement explains our policy regarding the collection, use, disclosure and protection of Personal Data. This privacy statement applies to the collection and use of Personal Data about you by Natco Foods Limited and their affiliates (“Natco”, “we” or “us”). In certain circumstances, we may provide you with additional information about our use of your Personal Data in specific circumstances, for example as part of a special offer or specific services.  Since we regularly review our policies and practices, your comments are always welcome. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time.
Children:  We do not intend to collect information from children who are under 18 years of age. If you are under 18, please do not provide information to us.
A. What is Personal Data?
Personal Data is information relating to an identified or identifiable individual, such as a name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, debit/credit card number or any photograph included on your Natco membership card, Internet (IP) address and information about an individual’s purchases and online shopping.
Personal Data does not include "aggregate" information. Aggregate information is data we collect about a group or category of products, services or customers, from which individual customers cannot be identified. In other words, information about how you use a service may be collected and combined with information about how others use the same service, but no Personal Data will be included in the resulting data. Likewise, information about the products you purchase may be collected and combined with information about the products purchased by others. Aggregate data helps us understand trends and customer needs so that we can better consider new products and services, and tailor existing products and services to customer desires.
B. Collection of Personal Data
We collect Personal Data when you:
•    Register to use and/or natcofoods.com or natcocc.com or agree to receive news about specials or other promotions;
•    Place an order or purchase products or services, at our Cash and Carry or online, or return or exchange items;
•    Contact us for any reason including questions, enquiries, comments, complaints or requests; such as by replying to enquiries by mail or fax, by telephone or in person at one of our locations;
•    Sign up for or renew your Natco Cash and Carry membership (including information about your credit history that may be collected, used, or disclosed if you choose to pay by cheque);
•    Add an additional cardholder to your account;
We may also take video footage on our properties to protect the rights, property or safety of Natco Foods Limited, Natco Cash and Carry, its customers, employees, or the public.
In addition, we automatically collect some information when you visit our website, This information may be collected through the use of "cookies" and web beacons. Please see our Cookie Policy for more details.
C. Use of Personal Data by Natco
The Personal Data we collect is generally used to process your requests or transactions, validate your membership, provide you with high-quality service, tell you about opportunities we think will be of interest and administer your account, including distribution of our own surveys and publications. For example, we may use your telephone number, your e-mail or your postal address to:
•    Approve you as a member when you apply for membership;
•    Manage the provision of goods and services to you, including monitoring your membership, processing exchanges or returns, to conduct a credit check if you choose to pay by cheque, to determine your credit status and for fraud detection and identification purposes;
•    Manage invoicing, accounting and information security services related to our transactions with you;
•    Protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Natco, its customers, employees, or the public;
•    Send notifications (via email or SMS/text message) related to your purchases, such as purchase confirmations or delivery schedules;
•    Alert you about product recalls or safety issues;
Provide you with news, promotional information, offers, other information from Natco and selected partners and product recommendations ("Promotional Information"). You may contact us at any time to decline Promotional Information (see H. Withdrawing Consent/Updating Your Personal Data below).
D. Sharing of Personal Data
We share information in these circumstances:
•    Order Fulfilment
We may provide to a third party information necessary to process a transaction or fulfil an order you have placed with us. For example, if you pay by a debit/credit card, your card number and sales transaction information are passed on to the card processor and/or issuer (including their service providers such as fraud verification services). However, we give suppliers, and others involved in the distribution chain only the information needed to provide you the products or services you order, such as shipping and/or billing address, e-mail address, telephone number and product orders. We are not responsible for any information you provide directly to these parties, and we encourage you to become familiar with their practices before disclosing information directly to them.
•    Service Providers and Contractors
From time to time we engage unaffiliated third parties and their affiliates, agents and subcontractors (“Service Providers”) to perform certain technological or administrative services on our behalf. For example, we retain companies to process debit and credit card payments. We may also use a Service Provider to host and administer one or more of our Sites, process and store data, and fulfil similar technology-related functions on our behalf. In these circumstances, the Personal Data that the Service Provider receives is limited to only the Personal Data held by us that they need in order to render their service to us.
If any of these service providers need access to your Personal Data, we require them to use it only to perform the services for us. We also require that they maintain the confidentiality of the information and/or return the information to us when they no longer need it.
We may disclose Personal Data without your knowledge or consent if a court order legally authorises us or requires us to do so. We may also disclose Personal Data to protect the rights, property or personal safety of Natco, its customers, employees or other members of the public. Except as set out above, we do not sell, rent, share or disclose the Personal Data we hold without your consent.
E. Other Uses and Disclosures
We may provide to our Service Providers the Personal Data necessary to allow them to offer or provide any benefits to which you are entitled under the terms of your Natco membership. In addition, we may use or disclose Personal Data in the good faith belief that we are lawfully authorised to do so, or that doing so is reasonably necessary to protect you, to comply with legal process or authorities, to respond to any claims, or to protect the rights, property or personal safety of the Natco Companies, our shoppers, Natco’s Members and subscribers, our employees or the public. This includes disclosure of information to control or investigate fraud. Personal Data, may be disclosed or transferred as part of, or during negotiations of, any merger or sale of company assets or acquisition.
F. Protection of Online Personal Information
Online account information is accessible only by using a password. You must keep your password confidential. You are responsible for all uses of www.Natcofoods.com. Or www.natcocc.com by anyone using your password. Please advise us immediately if you believe your password has been misused.
G. Withdrawing Consent/Updating Your Personal Data
We aim to keep it really simple in terms of how you can withdraw consent to receive promotional information from us and how you can update your personal details.
If you no longer wish to receive any marketing information from us and/or would like to be removed from our database, please let us know in one of the following ways:
•    Call – please call our head office in Buckingham on 01280 825 430
•    Email – Data Protection Team on dataprotectionteam@natcofoods.com
•    Write - Data Protection Team, Natco Foods Ltd, Choithram House, Swan Business Park, Buckingham, MK18 1TB
H. Questions or Concerns
If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy statement or would like to contact us for any reason, please contact us by email at dataprotectionteam@natcofoods.com; or in writing at Data Protection Team at Natco Foods Limited, Choithram House, Swan Business Park, Buckingham MK18 1TB
I. Cookie Policy
Natco Foods Limited (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the websites natcofoods.com and natcocc.com (the “Service”).
What are cookies?
Cookies are small pieces of text sent to your web browser by a website you visit. A cookie file is stored in your web browser and allows the Service or a third party to recognise you and make your next visit easier and the Service more useful to you.
Cookies can be “persistent” or “session” cookies. Persistent cookies remain on your personal computer or mobile device when you go offline, while session cookies are deleted as soon as you close your web browser.
How we use cookies
When you use and access the Service, we may place a number of cookie files in your web browser.
This Service may use cookies for the following purposes:
•    To enable certain functions of the Service
•    To provide analytics
•    To store your preferences
Third party cookies
In addition to our own cookies, our Service may also use various third parties cookies to report usage statistics of the Service, deliver advertisements on and through the Service, and so on. These may include analytics cookies, used to track information on how the Service is used, so that we can make improvements. We may also use analytics cookies to test new advertisements, pages, features or new functionality of the Service to see how our users react to them.
What are your choices regarding cookies
If you’d like to delete cookies or instruct your web browser to delete or refuse cookies, please visit the help pages of your web browser.
Please note, however, that if you delete cookies or refuse to accept them, you might not be able to use all of the features we offer, you may not be able to store your preferences, and some of our pages might not display properly.
Listed here are the commonly used web browsers, with link to their support pages containing information on how to delete or refuse cookies:
•    Google Chrome
•    Microsoft Edge
•    Microsoft Internet Explorer
•    Mozilla Firefox
•    Safari
For any other web browser, please visit your web browser’s official web pages.
You can also learn more about cookies at the following third party websites:
•    AllAboutCookies
•    Network Advertising Initiative
J. Changes to this Statement
We may change this Privacy Policy at any time, but will alert you that changes have been made by indicating at the top of the Privacy Policy the date it was last updated. We encourage you to review our privacy statement to make sure you understand how your Personal Data will be used. If we make a material change to how we use Personal Data and the new uses are unrelated to uses we disclose in this statement, we will communicate the changes in advance.
